If it spreads, you're dead.
Cold Storage is a comedy, science fiction, thriller
film directed by Jonny Campbell.
When a mutating, highly contagious fungus escapes a sealed facility, two young employees – joined by a grizzled
bioterror operative – must survive the wildest night shift ever to save humanity from extinction.
Naomi Williams, played by Georgina Campbell.
Travis 'Teacake' Meacham, played by Joe Keery.
Robert Quinn, played by Liam Neeson.
Dr. Hero Martins, played by Sosie Bacon.
Ma Rooney, played by Vanessa Redgrave.
Trini Romano, played by Lesley Manville.
Cold Storage is an upcoming comedy horror film directed by Jonny Campbell from a
screenplay by David Koepp, based on the 2019 titular novel by Koepp.
The film stars Georgina Campbell, Joe Keery, Sosie Bacon,
Vanessa Redgrave, Lesley Manville, and Liam Neeson.
It follows the attempts at containing a parasitic fungus
that leaks out of an abandoned military base.
Cold Storage is scheduled to be released in Mexico and Brazil on January 29,
2026, in the United States by Samuel Goldwyn Films on February 13.
StudioCanal is releasing Cold Storage in Poland on February 6, in France on February 18, in Germany
on February 19, in the United Kingdom on February 20, and in New Zealand on March 12.
The film explores themes of mutation, survival, lethal virus, epidemic, virus.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking and intense.